bankrollmob.com 2018-11-23

# Privacy Policy & Cookie Policy - BankrollMob

_Last updated: May 24, 2018._

* * *

Your privacy is important to BankrollMob.com. We strive to ensure that all your information are kept in strict confidence and will never be sold, rented, reused or otherwise publicized without you explicit consent. In order to identify you with the gaming providers (usually poker sites) and to avoid fraud, some of your information, provided by yourself, may be shared with the provider, if you request a bonus that needs to be issued to your account by the provider. 

This Privacy Policy further explains how we collect, use, share and protect your information. 

## 1\. Information we collect

### 1.1 Information you give us

**Account information:** When you sign-up at our site for a "Mob Account", we require your full name, address (street, zip code and city), country, e-mail address, gender and date of birth. You will also need to select a username and password, which is needed to log-in to your Mob Account in the future. All information, except your chosen username and country, is kept private and not visibile to the public. By creating a Mob Account you become part of a community where you may have access to multiple gaming-related offers and bonuses, therefor we require your personal information in order to approve your account before you get access, this is to combat fraud and ensure only one account per person. 

**Identity authentication:** We may ask you to verify your identity by either completing our free phone verification (a machine gives you a code that you need to confirm, either by phone call or text message) and/or by uploading a picture/scan of your ID (e.g. drivers license, passport, national ID, etc.). This is a requirement set by many of the bonus providers, as they rely on us to make sure a user does not receive multiple bonuses (to avoid fraud). Your ID is never shared with anyone, including our partners/providers, it is only for internal identity authentication. Sometimes we may ask you for further identification, e.g. holding your ID up next to your face while taking a photo (to confirm it's you on the ID), or by writing a code on a piece of paper and take a picture of the code next to your ID. Your identification document(s) is automatically deleted from our server after 1 year. 

**Communication with us and other members:** If you correspond with us via e-mail or our internal messaging system, we may retain the content of your messages and contact details and our replies. Information you post in our discussion forum, is accessible and viewable by the public. Communication with us via e-mail is either saved on our server in a mailbox or on Zendesk, which is our ticketing system provider (a data processor and certified compliance with EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield frameworks) with who we have a Data Processing Agreement ("DPA"). 

**Payment information:** We do not collect or store any payment information related to payment going from you to us. We do however store your payment information if you ever need to convert your Mob Points (the currency we use on BankrollMob.com to pay for affiliate/referrals, prizes etc.) to real money (USD, EUR), then we need your payment information for NetEller, Skrill, PayPal or whatever method you request your Mob Points converted and transferred to. This is usually just an account number, username, e-mail address or similar, and does not allow us collect payment from you, only to send payment to you. 

### 1.2 Information we automatically collect from your use of our website

**Usage information:** We collect information about your interactions with our website, such as the pages and content you view, sometimes which bonuses you may request (as we need to process your request). 

**Transaction information:** If you perform actions, such as winning a prize or referring new members to our site, you may earn Mob Points. We log information related to this, to keep an updated Mob Points balance for your account. 

**Location information:** We log your IP address when you log-in to BankrollMob, the IP address can give an estimation of which country you are visiting from, but can not be used by us to directly identify you only by the IP address. 

**Cookies:** We use cookies, including third party cookies, to distinguish you from other users and enhance your browsing experience on our webiste and to serve relevant content. Please refer to our Cookie Policy for more information. 

## 2\. Sharing & Disclosure

**Sharing between users and public information:** Only your username and country, selected when creating an account, is shared with the public. If you provide futher information on our site, such as public made forum posts or comments on news articles, a profile description etc., this information will also be shared with the public. Your private information is never shared, except in cases where you may have signed up at our site through a referral link (via an affiliate), the affiliate can see your first name in his affiliate-list but no further information. 

**External partners/providers:** We may share your personal information (name, address, e-mail address etc.) with our bonus providers. Your ID (e.g. passport) and/or identification documents will never be shared. When you request a bonus from a provider on our site, you need to submit your account information from that site, to us, so we can instruct the site to transfer the bonus to you, except when it is possible for us to do the transfer directly to your account. In this process, your personal information may sometimes be sent back to the provider to confirm the bonus is being paid to the correct user and to match your information with the information you provided to the bonus provider. Your name, e-mail address and country will also be shared with our e-mail marketing provider (iContact) to send you information, updates and promotional offers. You can always unsubscribe from these updates. 

**Data analysis tools:** We use Google Analytics with "anonymized IP"-enabled to help us understand how users are using our website. No personal information is ever sent to Google Analytics. Facebook is also integrated which means your usage will be tracked by Facebook as well, please refer to our Cookie Policy for more information. 

**Safety & Compliance with law:** We may also share personal information, only if it's necessary to comply with any applicable law or regulation, for example to investigate any violations or suspicions of criminal behaviour. 

**Aggregated data:** We may also aggregate and anonymize your information and share the anonymized and/or aggregated data with third parties for the purpose of industry and market analysis, advertising or other business purposes. This information is non-personally identifiable and cannot be used to identify you. 

## 3\. Other important information

### 3.1 Data retention

Any information you provide to us will be stored on our server and in backups for a commerically reasonable time. 

## 4\. Your choices

### 4.1 Updating your information

Please contact us if you ever wish to update your account information with us. 

### 4.2 Communications

You can always opt-out (unsubscribe) from our e-mail newsletters/marketing by using either an "Unsubscribe" or "Manage Your Subscription" link at the bottom of our e-mails. This is an easy and safe method to unsubscribe that will be respected. We use iContact as our e-mail marketing provider, who has a no tolerance spam policy (see: [iContact Anti-Spam Policy](https://www.icontact.com/legal/anti-spam-policy)). 

### 4.3 Review and delete your information

You may request in writing copies of your personal information held by us. We will provide you with a copy of the reasonable personal information held by us as soon as practicable and in no more than 30 days after receiving a valid request in writing. We may request proof of identification to verify your identity and validate the request. If your personal information, that we hold, is no longer up-to-date, let us know so we can update the information (as per point 4.1 in our Privacy Policy). You may also request the erasure of your personal information in accordance with the relevant data protection legislation, we will notify you within 30 days of your valid request about the relevant action taken. For technical reasons and to avoid fraud, we may decide to anonymize your data instead of deleting them, this is a one-way anonymization which prevents us from reading your information in the future, but still allows us to compare new accounts with older accounts, with a certain probability, to avoid multiple accounts being created with the same personal information. 

## 5\. Security

We take several security measures to keep your information safe and private while stored on our server and to protect against unauthorized access. Our server is located behind a physical firewall that inspects all traffic. 

When creating an account on our website, before storing your password, we apply a cryptographically secure hashing algorithm to it. Your password is therefor never stored in our database, but only a one-way encryption version. We can not read your password. 

## 6\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

BankrollMob.com reserves the right to change or replace this Piracy Policy at any time, we therefore ask you to check this page on a regular basis. The date of last update can be found at the top of our Privacy Policy & Cookie Policy page. 

## 7\. Contact

If you should have any questions or comments about our privacy policy please use our contact form. 

* * *

This Cookie Policy explains what cookies are and how we use them on our website. By using our website you are agreeing that we can use cookies in accordance with this policy. 

## What are cookies?

Cookies are small text files that are stored in the browser on your device, which contains small information. 

## How we use cookies

We use cookies to distinguish you from other users on our website and to enhance your browsing experience, by serving content that is as relevant to you as possible, and to keep your log-in details (temporary or for auto-login) when you log-in to your account on our website. 

## What type of cookies we use

Cookies exists as both session cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies are deleted automatically from your browser when you close it or have left our website for a while. Persistent cookies remain stored in your browser until a set expire date, which depends on their use, e.g. cookies that will allow you to automatic log-in to your account on our website will expire 2 years into the future, unless you clear your cookies or manually log-out. We also use cookies from Google Analytics to help analyze how visitors use our site. Facebook will also use cookies to log device information and activity information, without any further action from you, this occurs whether or not you have a Facebook account or are logged in to Facebook. 

## How to block cookies

Most browsers allow you to refuse cookies via a setting. If you block our use of cookies, or cookies in general, you may be unable to use certain features of our site and in general have a poorer user experience. 

## Changes to this Cookie Policy

BankrollMob.com reserves the right to change or replace this Cookie Policy at any time, we therefore ask you to check this page on a regular basis. The date of last update can be found at the top of our Privacy Policy & Cookie Policy page.
